DANIEL **ROMERO**

13420 Doty Ave, Hawthorne, CA 90250 | (714) 679-6375 danny@dannys.io | github@dannyk08 | linkedin@dannyk08

Summary

Three years of experience developing, and maintaining, web applications using modern frameworks and practices. I am looking for a Mid Front End Developer position at a company where there's a large emphasis on mentorship, growth, and building maintainable applications with modern tools.

Notable Skills

2017 - React, React Native, Redux, Jest, Angular 4, Webpack 2, AWS S3

2016 - Angular 1 & 2, NodeJS, ExpressJS, Typescript, Coffeescript, GruntJS, GulpJS, RethinkDB, Material UI

2015 - Jade, Foundation 5, HTML5, SASS, CSS3, jQuery

Experience

Mobile Developer

November 2017 - December 2017

ForceField

Los Angeles, CA

• Worked as a contractor to improve offline mobile experience for ForceField's Child Android application.

Front End Developer

July 2017 - October 2017

Winc (Formerly ClubW)

Los Angeles, CA

- Maintained and updated Winc's internal administrative system used for managing membership accounts and warehouse inventory. Reduced incidence of bugs and streamlined internal workflows.
- Partnered with internal teams to create new features like FedEx hold location integration, a tag based search engine, image uploader and cropper, dynamic partnership on our products detail page.
- Contributed as main front-end stakeholder in a sprint dedicated to improving current member experience, which increased total company revenue.

Junior Front End Developer

September 2015 - July 2017

Winc (Formerly ClubW)

Los Angeles, CA

Established specifications and developed a customizable landing page generator and content
management system. Empowered the marketing team to create their own customized landing pages,
greatly reducing the time and engineering resources needed to launch new marketing campaigns.

Web Development Intern

June 2015 - September 2015

ClubW

Los Angeles, CA

• Crafted more than one hundred landing pages for the marketing team that aligned messaging throughout the funnel via raw HTML5, CSS3, and Javascript.

Education

Full Stack Web Development Immersive

November 2014 - February 2015

General Assembly

Santa Monica, CA

A.A.S in Biology & A.A. in General Science

August 2008 - August 2014

Golden West College

Huntington Beach, CA